<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blogs on Odyssey of Julius</title><link>https://blog.tuuturu.io/en/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blogs on Odyssey of Julius</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.tuuturu.io/en/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Old Road to Vivestad</title><link>https://blog.tuuturu.io/en/blog/old-roads/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.tuuturu.io/en/blog/old-roads/</guid><description>Have you ever had a friend who could turn any ordinary day into an extraordinary adventure? Well, I have a friend like that - Kim. One day, out of the blue, he sent me a text message that would set the wheels in motion for a memorable motorcycle trip. The conversation went something like this: Kim initiated the trip with a text message. The conversation went something like this:</description></item><item><title>Mykle: A Cold Night's Adventure</title><link>https://blog.tuuturu.io/en/blog/winter-is-coming/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.tuuturu.io/en/blog/winter-is-coming/</guid><description>Chasing the Hammock Dreams: A Cold Night&amp;rsquo;s Adventure A sudden urge overcame me – the need to escape to nature and slumber beneath the stars in my trusty hammock. These cravings for outdoor solitude strike every now and then, and this time, I had a particular place in mind: a serene lake known as Mykle . My hope was to discover uncharted gravel roads and bask in the thrill of the unknown.</description></item><item><title>Learning the Ropes of Off-Road Riding</title><link>https://blog.tuuturu.io/en/blog/slow-climb/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.tuuturu.io/en/blog/slow-climb/</guid><description>Setting Off on a Rainy Day My friend Kim and I embarked on a ride with a mission: to master the art of identifying gravel and off-road paths, embrace the thrill of these terrains, and dive headfirst into our newfound hobby. The sky had been weeping for quite some time, and despite my comprehensive waterproof gear, droplets were finding their way in. But Kim and I, seasoned riders through countless journeys, found solace in the rain.</description></item><item><title>Exploring the Woods and Dropping the Bike</title><link>https://blog.tuuturu.io/en/blog/it-begins/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.tuuturu.io/en/blog/it-begins/</guid><description>Mind blowing realizations Wet stuff is slippery (WHAT!?) Good boots are important, your foot can get caught beneath 200kilos of bike (surprised pikachu face) 200kg is heavy (physics never seize to baffle me) Intro My girlfriend surprised me one day with an invitation to go mushroom picking. Now, I have to admit, I&amp;rsquo;m not particularly fond of mushrooms, and at that moment, the allure of staying in and being lazy was strong.</description></item></channel></rss>